http://www.thehockeyshop.com/pages/privacy-policy

Submit
Filter:
Junior
Youth (4-7)
Toddler (2-4T)
Infant (18M)
Junior
Youth (4-7)
Toddler (2-4T)
Infant (18M)
Our Privacy Policy Regarding Your Personal Information
The Hockey Shop is committed to protecting your privacy. That's why we've developed this Privacy Policy regarding our use of personal information collected in connection with our contests, electronic newsletters, surveys flyers, and other communications.
You should also know that Canadians have certain rights to privacy under The Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA) and Canada’s Anti-Spam Legislation (CASL), which address the collection, storage and use of personal information by organizations in the private sector.
We Are Committed to and Guarantee your Privacy
The Hockey Shop will not sell, distribute, barter, transfer or otherwise share any personally identifiable information obtained about our users to a third party, unless required by law. We do not sell lists.
When do we collect personal information and how will we use this information?
The Hockey Shop does not automatically collect any personally identifiable information. Such information is submitted with consent by visitors to our website and to our retail store, for such reasons as entering contests, taking part in promotions, answering surveys, and/or subscribing to newsletters, or other informational or promotional vehicles. The Hockey Shop collects your name, address, city, postal code, phone number, mobile phone number, email address, date of birth, and favorite sports. Your submission of this information is completely voluntary. This information will be used by The Hockey Shop to communicate with you for the purpose with which it was collected. These communications, unless otherwise stated, support our marketing, promotion, and information programs. The information is also used to conduct prize drawings and to notify the winners of the various contests we run. By submitting consent to The Hockey Shop you agree to its use for the purposes stated within this policy.
Who Can Access Your Personal Information Collected By The Hockey Shop?
Your personal information is strictly controlled and accessible only by employees who require this information to better serve you and/or improve our performance both in-store and on this website.
We do use a reputable third party service provider that assists us with this website and other important programs that allow us to serve you. This third party has signed an agreement of confidentially that states that all customer information remains confidential.
The Hockey Shop has no control over any information shared with another website prior to or after entering thehockeyshop.com from said website or portal. We track all traffic to and from our website and we guarantee that we will not share your personal information with a third party unless you give us permission to do so.
The Hockey Shop executes contests and promotions in our store and on thehockeyshop.com that are sometimes sponsored by a third party. You will be informed if we will share your information with a third party and you will have the option to choose whether or not you wish to participate in said contest or promotion.
Links
thehockeyshop.com contains links to other websites and is not responsible for any information submitted on these sites. The Hockey Shop is not responsible for the privacy practices of any of the sites that may be linked to thehockeyshop.com.
Your Consent
All information submitted to thehockeyshop.com is completely voluntary. Any time you submit your information when entering a contest, promotion, answer a survey or enroll for any of our promotional tools you will be given the option to consent to the collection and use of your personal information by The Hockey Shop for the purposes set out in this policy.
The Hockey Shop takes all necessary precautions to protect the security of your information.
Any requests regarding this policy must be made to info@thehockeyshop.com
The effective date of this privacy policy is June 25, 2014. The Hockey Shop reserves the right to update this policy without warning or notice.
